So how in this video I am going to show you
how you can do tractor insurance online from CSC. If you have a
CSC center then you
can insure any vehicle but in this video
I am going to
show you the complete process of doing tractor insurance. So let's get
started with a video. All you have to do is
open Google Chrome or Mozilla Firefox browser. So I
appoint Mozilla Firefox browser from here.
After that you have to search in Google here by
taking Digital Seva Portal.
Okay, so I search here by taking Digital Seva Portal
and as soon as you
search by taking Digital Seva Portal, an
interface will be displayed in front of you like this. So the
first link you will find is Digital Seva
Portal. You have to click on it. Okay, so
I click here and after clicking here
you have to
log in by clicking on login and entering CSC ID and password
but if you have already logged in here then
I click on debit
and after clicking on debit
you will be successfully logged in to the portal.
Okay and this kind of
interface will appear in front of you.  If you go there, you will have to click on insurance here to
insure any vehicle,
okay, so I clicked and after clicking, you will see a
school like this in front of you and on the
left side you will find a mill
and thatch at the bottom, so you have to click in it to do third
party insurance and motor
insurance, you have to click in it to do fast insurance,
okay, so I am going to do third party
insurance for tractor, so
from here many companies are given,
so you can do it from any company,
I am going to do Adi A insurance, okay, so
see, it is written ICICI Lombard General
Insurance, click here,
click on it, there is a sequence portal,
it will open like this, so see,
on the left side you will get the option of fast
and on the right side you will find a slap, so
for insuring the tractor,
Mi HTTP is written, TP means
third party, okay, after that you have to click on this cut court
and as soon as you click on gate,
first you will have to
enter the registration number, that is the number of the vehicle
which is given in the RC, you will enter it there,
so I will
enter the number of the vehicle here and  After entering the vehicle number,
you will have to enter the RTO, it
is written above ctrl + dkar is registered, okay, so you have to
enter the district where you have got your registration certificate i.e. RC made,
you will have to enter the name of that district,
okay, so I have put the color number here,
after entering that you will have to
enter the fast registration,
you will get it in the RC, so you have to select the fast station update from
here, okay, so
I lead festival dates here and
after selecting the registration date,
you will have to go down and from here you have to select the customer
state i.e. the state in which you have done your
registration,
so I select it from here,
after that I have to select the fixer here,
which company's officer is it,
you will have to select it from here, so from
here I select Mahindra &
Mahindra Saurabh on the manufacturer, it is Saurabh's
tractor which I am going to insure at the moment,
okay, so
after straightening, from here you have to select the text and this used
only for agriculture and forestry,
after that you have to set this model
number, which is the model number of the tractor
So I select this Airtel
number, so I add the number from here
because the tractor whose model number I am going to
enter is Saurav's
850, okay, after that
you have to enter the number and five numbers after entering the school,
so I enter this number from here,
after entering the engine number, chassis number, you have to
select here which tractor
I have set, you should find it, so
I entered 2013 here,
after that you have to select here
and you have to fold downwards,
okay,
I darken the school here,
after that you have to click on get cot, as
soon as you click on get,
here you will have to make the payment for the transients,
it will come here, okay, so see, the
most
important thing you will have to pay is for the third party,
okay,
after that you have to click on create new customer here to
enter the customer details, after that you have to
select here, then the title is mister,
after that you have to write the name in whose name the tractor
is, okay, so
you will get all this from the art  If it goes
there, you will have to enter it,
I will tell you the name here,
after entering the name you do not have to enter the date of birth, you have to enter the same
which is marked with a star,
so enter the name of the father
which is in the RC,
you put the same in the registration certificate here,
after that cross I have to
enter the complete address in this dress which is
given in today, village post this place
district pin code, all of them have to be entered,
after that you have to enter the pin number, so I enter the
number here again,
after entering the pin number the city name will
automatically come, so select it from here
and after selecting, the
district and state will automatically come here,
after that you have to enter the email ID mobile
number here, so I enter the email ID here
and after entering the email ID you have to
enter the mobile number of the person whose car it is, you have to enter the mobile
number here, so
after entering the email ID and mobile number
you have to scroll down a bit,
after that click on get professional here,
so I click on get proper here,
after clicking on get, you will
get an option by policy here, you have to
click on it and after clicking this
CSC ID  You will have to enter the password,
after that you have to enter the wallet PIN and as soon as you
enter it, the payment will be successful and
after the payment is successful you will
get the option to download, so you
can download the insurance by clicking on download, but there is
no money in your CSC wallet at the moment, so if you are on
payment then see this drop coat
10 inch white sines wallet balance, that is, there is
no money in my CSC wallet at the moment, okay, so
whenever you will insure any vehicle, be it a
tractor or
any other vehicle, then before clicking on buy SIM,
you will have to add money to the CSC wallet,
after that you have to click on bar police,
okay, so in this way you
can insure the tractor from CSC, so guys that's all
in this video, I
hope you liked the video, if
you liked the video then do not forget to like this video and
subscribe to this channel, to
see such videos in the future,
thanks for watching these videos and always keep a
smiling face